Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files: Subject Files MS 3009-RG 13.Series III
New-York Historical Society
Time Inc. Time Research Center Files: Subject Files
1926-2000
New-York Historical Society
Time, inc.
MS 3009-RG 13.Series III
774 Linear feet
This finding aid contains the detailed folder list of the Time Research Center Subject Files for the purpose of in-depth keyword searching. Please make requests for the material from MS 3009-RG 13 which is the full version of the finding aid.
Scope and Contents
This finding aid contains the detailed folder list of the Time Research Center Subject Files for the purpose of in-depth keyword searching.
Please make requests for the material from MS 3009-RG 13 which is the full version of the finding aid.
- Series III. Subject Files, 1926-2000; 774 Linear feet (774 boxes)
  Scope and Contents
  The Subject Files contain research materials related to common headline news topics that were used by reporters and researchers at magazines across Time Inc. Major topics covered include weapons and wars, geographic regions, populations of the United States and the Soviet Republic, domestic and international press organizations, United States elections, and word usage. Topics are frequently divided into sub-topics. For example, the files on New York City include boroughs, neighborhoods, government departments and agencies, parks, and extended folders on different streets.
  Because these files were heavily used, there is some amount of misfiling.
  The majority of materials within the Subject Files are magazine and newspaper clippings. Other types of materials include article correction, correspondent dispatches, correspondence between reporters, correspondence between reporters and editors, correspondence from the general public to magazine editors, transcripts of interviews and speeches as well as press conferences, summaries of interviews, editorial outlines for articles, government and foreign policy overviews, press releases, press kits, event schedules and programs, lists of contacts and committee members as well as research sources, lists of award winners, pamphlets, drafts of articles, academic and scientific papers, financial reports, photos, congressional reports, and factsheets.
  Arrangement
  Based on the original order, the Subject Files are organized alphabetically by topic then sub-topics. Multiple folders on the same topic or sub-topic are further organized in reverse chronological order.
  - Atomic Weapons, 1945-1993 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 1-2)
  - Atomic Weapons: A-D, 1957-1963, 1969-1993 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 3)
  - Atomic Weapons: E-L, 1959-1963, 1971-1985, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Weapons: M-P, 1957-1993 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 5)
  - Atomic Weapons: R-Z, 1957-1964, 1974-1993 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 6)
  - Atomic Weapons: Africa, 1960-1965, 1974, 1980 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 7)
  - Atomic Weapons: Algeria, 1974, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Weapons: Amateur, 1969-1979 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Weapons: Argentina, 1951-1952, 1967-1992 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Weapons: Brazil, 1975-1990 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Weapons: China, 1954-1993 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 12-23)
  - Atomic Weapons: Cobalt, 1954-1955, 1961-1965, 1981 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 24)
  - Atomic Weapons: Commonwealth of Independent States, 1993 (Offsite-box 1705, Folder 25)
  - Atomic Weapons: Commonwealth of Independent States, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 1-2)
  - Atomic Weapons: Communist Countries, 1956-1992 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 3)
  - Atomic Weapons: Cuba, 1963, 1978-1983, 1992 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Weapons: Defective, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 5)
  - Atomic Weapons: Defense Against, 1945-1968, 1975-1991 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 6-9)
  - Atomic Weapons: Detection, 1954-1993 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 10-21)
  - Atomic Weapons: East, Far, 1952, 1960, 1966-1979, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 22)
  - Atomic Weapons: East, Near, 1963-1983, 1990-1993 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 23)
  - Atomic Weapons: Effects, 1982-1990 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 24)
  - Atomic Weapons: Equipment, 1962-1992 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 25)
  - Atomic Weapons: Europe, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 1727, Folder 26-31)
  - Atomic Weapons: Europe, 1956-1977 (Offsite-box 1728, Folder 1-2)
  - Atomic Weapons: France, 1954-1993 (Offsite-box 1728, Folder 3-17)
  - Atomic Weapons: France and Great Britain, 1960-1973, 1979-1990 (Offsite-box 1728, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Weapons: Germany, 1960-1993 (Offsite-box 1728, Folder 19-25)
  - Atomic Weapons: Germany, 1944-1959 (Offsite-box 1729, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Weapons: Gravity Bombs, 1966 (Offsite-box 1729, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Weapons: Great Britain, 1946-1968, 1974-1993 (Offsite-box 1729, Folder 3-10)
  - Atomic Weapons: Great Britain and United States, 1957-1971, 1980-1981, 1986 (Offsite-box 1729, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Weapons: Greece, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 1729, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Weapons: India, 1962-1993 (Offsite-box 1729, Folder 13-17)
  - Atomic Weapons: Indonesia, 1964-1965 (Offsite-box 1729, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Weapons: International, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 1729, Folder 19-31)
  - Atomic Weapons: International, 1947-1980 (Offsite-box 1730, Folder 1-8)
  - Atomic Weapons: International: Testing, 1956-1993 (Offsite-box 1730, Folder 9-12)
  - Atomic Weapons: International: Testing: At Sea, 1971-1973, 1979-1980, 1992 (Offsite-box 1730, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Weapons: International: Testing: Number of Tests, 1963-1976, 1985-1987, undated (Offsite-box 1730, Folder 14)
  - Atomic Weapons: International: Testing: Space, 1946-1947, 1957-1963, 1972-1973, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 1730, Folder 15)
  - Atomic Weapons: Iran, 1959-1961, 1974-1976, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 1730, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Weapons: Iraq, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 1730, Folder 17-20)
  - Atomic Weapons: Iraq, 1959-1962, 1974, 1980-1991 (Offsite-box 1731, Folder 1-6)
  - Atomic Weapons: Israel, 1958-1993 (Offsite-box 1731, Folder 7-11)
  - Atomic Weapons: Italy, 1952, 1963-1967, 1980-1982, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 1731, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Weapons: Japan, 1955-1993 (Offsite-box 1731, Folder 13-15)
  - Atomic Weapons: Kazakhstan, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 1731, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Weapons: Korea, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 1731, Folder 17-21)
  - Atomic Weapons: Korea, 1955-1978, 1988-1990 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Weapons: Laser, 1973, 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Weapons: Latin America, 1962-1982, 1988-1992 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 3)
  - Atomic Weapons: Libya, 1975-1992 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Weapons: Materials, 1974-1993 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 5-6)
  - Atomic Weapons: Neutrons, 1960-1961, 1977-1993, undated (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 7-8)
  - Atomic Weapons: Neutron: Commonwealth of Independent States, 1992 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Weapons: Neutron: France, 1978-1985 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Weapons: Neutron: Great Britain, 1981 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Weapons: Neutron: International, 1960-1961, 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Weapons: Neutron: Korea, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Weapons: Neutron: Russia, 1991 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 14)
  - Atomic Weapons: Neutron: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1978-1984, 1991 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 15)
  - Atomic Weapons: Neutron: United States, 1959-1961, 1974-1981, 1992, undated (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 16-19)
  - Atomic Weapons: Nitrogen, 1954 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 20)
  - Atomic Weapons: North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 1732, Folder 21-26)
  - Atomic Weapons: North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1953-1978 (Offsite-box 1733, Folder 1-11)
  - Atomic Weapons: Pakistan, 1963-1967, 1974-1993 (Offsite-box 1733, Folder 12-21)
  - Atomic Weapons: Particle Beam, 1977-1989, undated (Offsite-box 1733, Folder 22)
  - Atomic Weapons: Physical Effects, 1985-1993 (Offsite-box 1733, Folder 23)
  - Atomic Weapons: Physical Effects, 1945-1984 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 1-13)
  - Atomic Weapons: Polls, 1978-1986 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 14)
  - Atomic Weapons: Production Methods, 1963-1991 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 15)
  - Atomic Weapons: Publications, 1965, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions, 1981-1990 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 17)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: A, 1964-1989 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Africa, 1959-1965 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 19)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Algeria, 1961-1963 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 20)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Argentina, 1954, 1985, 1991 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 21)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Australia, 1957-1964, 1972-1988 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 22)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Australia: Associations, 1987-1991 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 23)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: B, 1982-1987 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 24)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Belgium, 1962, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 25)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Brazil, 1966, 1977, 1991 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 26)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: C, 1983 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 27)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Canada, 1969-1975, 1982-1987 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 28)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Canada: Associations, 1984 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 29)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: China, 1954, 1961-1973, 1979-1991 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 30)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Communist Countries, 1968, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 1734, Folder 31)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Czechoslovakia, 1961, 1983-1988 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Denmark, 1961-1962, 1981-1988 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: East, Far, 1955-1960, 1986-1987 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 3)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: East, Near, 1960, 1968, 1974 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Europe, 1955, 1961-1966,1973-1988 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 5-13)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Europe: Associations, 1959, 1983 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 14)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: F, 1965, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 15)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Finland, 1957-1962, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: France, 1954-1991 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 17)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: France: Associations, 1960-1963, 1983-1985 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Germany, 1954-1969, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 19-27)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Germany: Associations, 1958-1960, 1968, 1978, 1983 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 28)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Ghana, 1960-1962 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 29)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Great Britain, 1986-1989 (Offsite-box 1735, Folder 30-32)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Great Britain, 1945-1948, 1954-1966, 1974-1985 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 1-9)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Great Britain: Associations, 1954-1963, 1970, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Great Britain: Associations: Campaign for Nuclear Disarmament, 1958-1969, 1981-1987 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 11-13)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Great Britain: Associations: Committee of One Hundred, 1960-1970 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 14-15)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Greece, 1981-1987 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Greece: Associations, 1967 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 17)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: I, 1970-1985, 1991 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: India, 1954-1991 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 19)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: India: Associations, 1965 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 20)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Indonesia, 1954-1958, 1965, 1987 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 21)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: International, 1945-1992 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 22-27)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: International: Associations, 1985 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 28)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Iran, 1974-1987 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 29)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Italy, 1952-1954, 1961, 1968-1969, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 30)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Japan, 1966-1993 (Offsite-box 1736, Folder 31-32)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Japan, 1954-1965 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Japan: Associations, 1957-1982, 1988, undated (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: K, 1964, 1985, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 3)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: L, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Latin America, 1961-1966, 1983 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 5)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: M, 1960-1961, 1982, 1989 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 6)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Marshall Islands, 1954, 1981-1982 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 7)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Mexico, 1961 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Morocco, 1959-1960 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: N, 1968-1989 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Netherlands, 1974-1985 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Netherlands: Associations, 1978-1982 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: New Zealand, 1961-1992 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 13-15)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: New Zealand: Associations, 1992 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Nigeria, 1960 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 17)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: P, 1981-1987 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Pakistan, 1961, 1974-1991 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 19)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Peru, 1961, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 20)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Philippines, 1961, 1973, 1982-1991 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 21)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Puerto Rico, 1961-1985 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 22)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Religious Groups, 1945-1986 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 23-31)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Religious Groups: Associations, 1979-1983 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 32)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Rumania, 1978-1983 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 33)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Russia, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 34)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Ryukyu Island: Associations, 1964-1969, 1989 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 35)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: S, 1962, 1968, 1976-1988 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 36)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Scandinavia, 1961, 1982-1987 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 37)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: South Africa, 1976-1980, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 38)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Sweden, 1961, 1973-1986 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 39)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Switzerland, 1968-1969, 1983 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 40)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Sudan, 1959-1961 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 41)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: T, 1962-1968, 1987-1991 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 42)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Tuamotu Islands, 1985 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 43)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: U, 1973, 1979-1984, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 44)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1965-1969, 1982-1991 (Offsite-box 1737, Folder 45-46)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1954-1963 (Offsite-box 1738, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics: Associations: Groups for the Establishment of Mutual Trust Between the U.S.A. and the U.S.S.R., 1982-1987 (Offsite-box 1738, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United Arab Republics, 1960-1961, 1969-1971 (Offsite-box 1738, Folder 3)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States, 1970-1992 (Offsite-box 1738, Folder 4-23)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States, 1945-1969, undated (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 1-7)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations, 1962, 1969, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: A-B, 1961, 1971, 1982-1988 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: C, 1962-1963, 1980-1981 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: D-L, 1963-1969, 1982-1990 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: M-P, 1957-1967, 1980-1992 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: Q-Z, 1957-1969, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: Committee for Nonviolent Action, 1960-1968 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 14-15)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: Committee for Nuclear Responsibility, 1971-1973 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 16)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: Educational Committee to Halt Atomic Weapons Spread, 1966-1969 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 17)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: Ground Zero, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, 1962-1970 (Offsite-box 1739, Folder 19-24)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: National Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, 1957-1961 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 1-3)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: Non-Violent Action Against Nuclear Weapons, 1957-1966 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: Nuclear Club, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 5)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Associations: SANE: Committee for a Sane Nuclear Policy, 1971-1990 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 6)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Great Peace March, 1985-1987, undated (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 7)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: United States: Teach-Ins, 1981-1984 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Vanuatu, 1987 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Yugoslavia, 1961, 1977 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reactions: Zambia, 1991 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Weapons: Records (Documents), 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 12)
  - Atomic Weapons: Records (Superlatives), 1962-1975, 1987-1992, undated (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 13)
  - Atomic Weapons: Reduced Residuals Radiation Bombs, 1978 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 14)
  - Atomic Weapons: Russia, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 15-17)
  - Atomic Weapons: Ryukyu Islands, 1969-1973 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Weapons: Satellites: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1979 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 19)
  - Atomic Weapons: Satellites, Atomic Weapons on, 1967-1970, 1978-1987 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 20)
  - Atomic Weapons: Satellites, Atomic Weapons on: International, 1960-1967 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 21)
  - Atomic Weapons: Satellites, Atomic Weapons on: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1962-1972, 1982-1983 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 22)
  - Atomic Weapons: Satellites, Atomic Weapons on: United States, 1960-1971, 1982 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 23)
  - Atomic Weapons: Size, 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 24)
  - Atomic Weapons: South Africa, 1969-1993, undated (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 25)
  - Atomic Weapons: Sweden, 1954-1962, 1981-1985 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 26)
  - Atomic Weapons: Switzerland, 1958-1966 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 27)
  - Atomic Weapons: Terminology, 1947, 1958-1966, 1979-1986, undated (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 28)
  - Atomic Weapons: Ukraine, 1991-1993 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 29-30)
  - Atomic Weapons: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1991 (Offsite-box 1740, Folder 31)
  - Atomic Weapons: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1968-1991 (Offsite-box 1741, Folder 1-20)
  - Atomic Weapons: Union of Soviet Socialist Republics, 1947-1967 (Offsite-box 1742, Folder 1-4)
  - Atomic Weapons: United Arab Republic, 1963-1974, 1988 (Offsite-box 1742, Folder 5)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 1742, Folder 6-18)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States, 1945-1981 (Offsite-box 1743, Folder 1-25)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: A-Z, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 1744, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Control of Use, 1964-1992 (Offsite-box 1744, Folder 2-4)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Deployment, 1967-1992 (Offsite-box 1744, Folder 5-13)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Description, 1966-1972, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 1744, Folder 14)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Education, 1969, 1981-1988 (Offsite-box 1744, Folder 15)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Hiroshima and Nagasaki Bombs, 1945-1946, 1958-1993, undated (Offsite-box 1744, Folder 16-24)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: History, 1965-1993 (Offsite-box 1744, Folder 25)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Labor, 1969, 1975, 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 1744, Folder 26)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Legislation, 1969, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 1744, Folder 27)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: News Coverage, 1968, 1979-1989 (Offsite-box 1745, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Number of, 1948-1953, 1960-1966, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 1745, Folder 2-6)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Personnel, 1971, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 1745, Folder 7)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Regulation, 1976-1978, 1988-1991 (Offsite-box 1745, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Research, 1975, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 1745, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: State, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 1745, Folder 10)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Storage, 1972-1975, 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 1745, Folder 11)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing, 1945-1993 (Offsite-box 1745, Folder 12-28)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Aleutian Islands, 1971-1975 (Offsite-box 1745, Folder 29-30)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Aleutian Islands, 1965-1970 (Offsite-box 1746, Folder 1)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: California, 1959, 1985-1992 (Offsite-box 1746, Folder 2)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Louisiana, 1960 (Offsite-box 1746, Folder 3)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Maryland, 1984 (Offsite-box 1746, Folder 4)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Mississippi, 1964-1967, 1979, 1990 (Offsite-box 1746, Folder 5)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Nevada, 1951-1993 (Offsite-box 1746, Folder 6-22)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: New Mexico, 1945-1952, 1960-1972, 1978-1989, undated (Offsite-box 1746, Folder 23)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Pacific Proving Ground, 1963-1993 (Offsite-box 1746, Folder 24-26)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Pacific Proving Ground, 1946-1962 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 1-17)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Project Argus, 1959-1961, 1979 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 18)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Texas, 1989 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 19)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Testing: Virginia, 1966-1967 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 20)
  - Atomic Weapons: United States: Transportation, 1965, 1971-1974, 1983-1989 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 21)
  - Atomic Weapons: Uses, 1974-1993 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 22)
  - Atomic Weapons: Uses: Demonstration Firing, 1981 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 23)
  - Atomic Weapons: Viet Nam, 1968-1969 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 24)
  - Awards: A-L, 1955-1991 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 25)
  - Awards: M-Z, 1948, 1958-1992 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 26)
  - Awards: Argentina, 1955-1960, 1971 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 27)
  - Awards: Australia, 1964-1969, 1975 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 28)
  - Awards: Denmark, 1959-1965, 1975 (Offsite-box 1790, Folder 29)